{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874254557","data":{"timestamp":" 946874254557"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874255535","data":{"timestamp":" 946874255534"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874258511","data":{"timestamp":" 946874258510"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874259053","data":{"timestamp":" 946874259053"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874259711","data":{"timestamp":" 946874259710"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874263910","data":{"timestamp":" 946874263910"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874264845","data":{"timestamp":" 946874264844"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874268508","data":{"timestamp":" 946874268508"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874269303","data":{"timestamp":" 946874269302"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874270288","data":{"timestamp":" 946874270287"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874274237","data":{"timestamp":" 946874274237"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874275212","data":{"timestamp":" 946874275211"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874278218","data":{"timestamp":" 946874278217"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874278760","data":{"timestamp":" 946874278759"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874279414","data":{"timestamp":" 946874279414"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874283639","data":{"timestamp":" 946874283639"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874284572","data":{"timestamp":" 946874284572"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874288308","data":{"timestamp":" 946874288308"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874289105","data":{"timestamp":" 946874289104"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874290093","data":{"timestamp":" 946874290092"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874293435","data":{"timestamp":" 946874293433"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874293522","data":{"timestamp":" 946874293522"," userId":" 6116001775"," sessionId":" 6116001775_20000103_073717"," gameId":" f02f9a81-5dc8-42e4-90f4-7260cf5efbba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}